Edward U. Condon Papers 1920-1974 Mss.B.C752
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1920-1974; 128 boxes, 64 linear feet
  - Way To Be Safe Is Never To Be Secure., Curtis, Charles P. (Box 59)
  - Curtis, Harvey L. (Box 59)
  - Curtiss, John H., 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Cushing, E. H. (Box 59)
  - Cushman, Robert E. (Box 59)
  - Cutter Laboratories (Box 59)
  - D. Van Nostrand Company, Inc. (Box 59)
  - Daddario, Emilio Q. - Sub-Committees, 4 folders (Box 59)
  - Dalton, Robert (Box 59)
  - Daniel, Robert (Box 59)
  - Danielson, Philip A. (Box 59)
  - Darley, Ward (Box 59)
  - Darrow, Karl K. (Box 59)
  - Dartmouth College (Box 60)
  - Dartmouth College: Great Issues Course, 5 folders (Box 60)
  - Darwin, Charles Galton (Box 60)
  - David, Edward E., Jr. (Box 60)
  - David, Nathan H., 5 folders (Box 60)
  - Davies, Clarence E. (Box 60)
  - Thermodynamic and Kinetic Properties of Glasses, Davies, R. O. and Jones, G. R. (Box 60)
  - Davis, Bernard D. (Box 60)
  - Davis, Charles R. (Box 60)
  - Davis, George F. (Box 60)
  - Key to Mystery Pulses: Rotating Neutron Stars, Davis, Harold L. (Box 60)
  - Davis, Kenneth E. (Box 60)
  - Dawson, Mrs. James, Sr. (Box 60)
  - Day, Ralph K. (Box 60)
  - Dayton, Bruce (Box 60)
  - Interpretation of the Solar Polarization, Debarbat, Suzanne, et al. (Box 60)
  - DeBenedetti, Sergio, 3 folders (Box 60)
  - Decker, William C. (Box 60)
  - Dedijer, Steven, 3 folders (Box 60)
  - Intelligence Policy, Dedijer, Steven. (Box 60)
  - Regional Research and Development Policy: The Example of Alaska., Dedijer, Steven. (Box 60)
  - Tito's Bomb, Dedijer, Steven. (Box 60)
  - Remarks on the Klauder Phenomenon, DeFacio, B. (Box 60)
  - Defenders of 3 Against HUAC (Box 60)
  - DeHeer, J. (Box 60)
  - Dehmer, J. L. The Phase-Amplitude Method in Atomic Physics (Box 60)
  - Dellums, Ronald V. (Box 60)
  - Democratic National Committee (Box 60)
  - Democratic State Central Committee, Colorado (Box 60)
  - Dempster, Richard R. (Box 60)
  - Dennes, William R. (Box 60)
  - Dennison, David M. (Box 60)
  - DePauw University (Box 60)
  - Desalination (Box 60)
  - Design, Inc. (Box 60)
  - Desmond, Thomas C. (Box 60)
  - Detectors, 4 folders (Box 60)
  - Dewey, W. (Box 61)
  - D'Heurle, François (Box 61)
  - Diamond, Hymen (Box 61)
  - Dicke, Robert H. (Box 61)
  - Dickinson College (Box 61)
  - Dieter, Nannielou H. (Box 61)
  - Dimock, Marshall (Box 61)
  - Ding Dong Dollar: Anti-Polaris Songs (anti-arms race songs, 1961) (Box 61)
  - Disarmament and Arms Control, 4 folders (Box 61)
  - Division of Peace and World Order (Box 61)
  - Dodds, H. W., 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Donner, Frank. The Informer (Box 61)
  - Doolittle, H. D. (Box 61)
  - Dorfman, Julius (Box 61)
  - Douglas, Mrs. Helen Gahagan (Box 61)
  - Societies and Citizens React to Attacks on Dr. Condon, Douglas, Helen Gahagan. (Box 61)
  - Douglas Advanced Research Laboratory, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Dover Publications, Inc. (Box 61)
  - Dresden, Max (Box 61)
  - Dressler, Robert F. (Box 61)
  - Drexel Institute of Technology (Box 61)
  - Driggins, John (Box 61)
  - Drummond, Roscoe (Box 61)
  - DuBridge, Lee Alvin, 3 folders (Box 61)
  - Dudley, Harold M. (Box 61)
  - Duffendack, O. S. (Box 61)
  - Duffey, E. J. (Box 61)
  - Duke, David (Box 61)
  - DuMond, Jesse W. M., 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Description of a Three-Weeks' Visit to the Soviet Union Under the USA-USSR Academy Exchange Agreement, 3 folders; DuMond, Jesse W. M., (Jesse William Monroe), 1892-1976 (Box 61)
  - Precision Measurements on Certain Fundamental Natural Constants of Physics and Chemistry, DuMond, Jesse W. M., (Jesse William Monroe), 1892-1976 (Box 61)
  - Addendum. Present Key Importance of the Fine Structure Constant..., DuMond, Jesse W. M., (Jesse William Monroe), 1892-1976 (Box 61)
  - Dunn, Leslie Clarence (Box 61)
  - Dunn, William L. (Box 61)
  - Durr, Clifford J., 7 folders (Box 61)
  - Durr, Clifford J. Science and the First Amendment (Box 61)
  - Durr, Virginia, 5 folders (Box 61)
  - Easby, Dudley T., Jr. (Box 61)
  - Eastern Industrial Personnel Security Board, 6 folders (Box 61)
  - Eastern Industrial Personnel Security Board. Hearing - April, 1954: Brief Before..., 10 folders (Box 61-62)
  - Eastern Industrial Personnel Security Board. Hearing - April, 1954: Transcript in the Case of E. U. C[ondon] Before..., 25 folders (Box 62)
  - Eastern Industrial Personnel Security Board. Memorandum in Behalf of E. U. Condon, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - Eastham, Melville (Box 62)
  - Eastland, James (Box 62)
  - Ecology (Box 62)
  - Edelstein, Julius C. C. (Box 62)
  - Edgewater Beach Hotel (Box 62)
  - Edlen, Bengt (Box 62)
  - Educational Conference - 14th Annual (Box 62)
  - Edwards, David F. (Box 62)
  - Egerton, John W. (Box 62)
  - Eighth International Quantum Electronics Conference - 1974 (Box 62)
  - Einstein, Albert (Box 62)
  - In Re: Einstein, Albert (Box 62)
  - Eiseman, John H. (Box 62)
  - Eisenbud, Leonard (Box 62)
  - Eisendrath, Marice. (Box 62)
    See: Bennett, John C., et al.
  - Eisenhart, Churchill (Box 62)
  - Reliability of Measured Values - Part One. Fundamental Concepts, Eisenhart, Churchill. (Box 62)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight David, 3 folders (Box 62)
  - Eisenhower, Milton, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - Electricity Lecture Notes. Physics 106. (Box 62)
    See: Course Materials. Physics 106
  - Electromagnetic Theory of Light (Box 62)
    See: Course Materials. Electromagnetic Theory of Light
  - Elements: 1. Hydrogen H, 5 folders (Box 62)
  - Elements: 2. Helium He, 7 folders (Box 62-63)
  - Elements: 3. Lithium Li, 5 folders (Box 63)
  - Elements: 4. Beryllium Be, 6 folders (Box 63)
  - Elements: 5. Boron B (Box 63)
  - Elements: 6. Carbon C, 6 folders (Box 63)
  - Elements: 7. Nitrogen N, 4 folders (Box 63)
  - Elements: 8. Oxygen O, 6 folders (Box 63)
  - Elements: 9. Fluorine F (Box 63)
  - Elements: 10. Neon Ne (Box 63)
  - Elements: 11. Sodium Na, 2 folders (Box 63)
  - Elements: 12. Magnesium Mg, 8 folders (Box 64)
  - Elements: 13. Aluminum Al, 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Elements: 14. Silicon Si, 3 folders (Box 64)
  - Elements: 15. Phosphorus P (Box 64)
  - Elements: 16. Sulphur S, 6 folders (Box 64)
  - Elements: 17. Chlorine Cl, 7 folders (Box 64)
  - Elements: 18. Argon AR, 7 folders (Box 64-65)
  - Elements: 19. Potassium K (Box 65)
  - Elements: 20. Calcium Ca, 6 folders (Box 65)
  - Elements: 21. Scandium Sc (Box 65)
  - Elements: 22. Titanium Ti (Box 65)
  - Elements: 23. Vanadium V (Box 65)
  - Elements: 24. Chromium Cr, 2 folders (Box 65)
  - Elements: 25. Manganese Mn, 3 folders (Box 65)
  - Elements: 26. Iron Fe, 7 folders (Box 65)
  - Elements: 27. Cobalt Co (Box 65)
  - Elements: 28. Nickel Ni (Box 65)
  - Elements: 29. Copper Cu, 2 folders (Box 65)
  - Elements: 30. Zinc Zn (Box 65)
  - Elements: 31. Gallium Ga, 4 folders (Box 65)
  - Elements: 32. Germanium Ge (Box 66)
  - Elements: 33. Arsenic As (Box 66)
  - Elements: 34. Selenium Se (Box 66)
  - Elements: 35. Bromine Br (Box 66)
  - Elements: 36. Krypton Kr (Box 66)
  - Elements: 37. Rubidium Rb (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 38. Strontium Sr (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 39. Yttrium Y (Box 66)
  - Elements: 40. Zirconium Zr (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 41. Niobium Nb (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 42. Molybdenum Mo (Box 66)
  - Elements: 43. Technetium Tc (Box 66)
  - Elements: 44. Ruthenium Ru, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Elements: 45. Rhodium Rh (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 46. Palladium Pd (Box 66)
  - Elements: 47. Silver Ag (Box 66)
  - Elements: 48. Cadmium Cd (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 49. Indium In (Box 66)
  - Elements: 50. Tin Sn (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 51. Antimony Sb (Box 66)
  - Elements: 52. Tellurium Te (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 53. Iodine I (Box 66)
  - Elements: 54. Xenon Xe, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Elements: 55. Cesium Ce, 4 folders (Box 66)
  - Elements: 56. Barium Ba (Box 66)
  - Elements: 57. Lanthanum La, 3 folders (Box 66)
  - Elements: 58. Cerium Ce (Box 66)
  - Elements: 59. Praseodymium Pr (Box 66)
  - Elements: 60. Neodymium Nd (Box 66)
  - Elements: 61. Promethium Pm (Box 66)
  - Elements: 62. Samarium Sm (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 63. Europium Eu (Box 66)
  - Elements: 64. Gadolinium Gd (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 65. Terbium Tb, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Elements: 66. Dysprosium Dy (Box 66)
  - Elements: 67. Holmium Ho (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 68. Erbium Er (Box 66)
  - Elements: 69. Thulium Tm (Box 66)
  - Elements: 70. Ytterbium Yb (Box 66)
  - Elements: 71. Lutetium Lu (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 72. Hafnium Hf (Box 66)
  - Elements: 73. Tantalum Ta (Box 66)
  - Elements: 74. Tungsten (Wolfram) W (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 75. Rhenium Re (Box 66)
  - Elements: 76. Osmium Os, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Elements: 77. Iridium Ir (Box 66)
  - Elements: 78. Platinum Pt (folder empty) (Box 66)
  - Elements: 79. Gold Au (Box 66)
  - Elements: 80. Mercury Hg, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Elements: 81. Thallium Tl (Box 66)
  - Elements: 82. Lead Pb, 4 folders (Box 67)
  - Elements: 83. Bismuth Bi (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 84. Polonium Po (Box 67)
  - Elements: 85. Astatine At (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 86. Radon Rn (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 87. Francium Fr (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 88. Radium Ra (Box 67)
  - Elements: 89. Actinium Ac (Box 67)
  - Elements: 90. Thorium Th, 3 folders (Box 67)
  - Elements: 91. Proctactinium Pa (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 92. Uranium U, 4 folders (Box 67)
  - Elements: 93. Neptunium Np (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 94. Plutonium Pu (Box 67)
  - Elements: 95. Americium Am (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 96. Curium Cm (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 97. Berkelium Bk (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 98. Californium Cf (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 99. Einsteinium Es (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 100. Fermium Fm (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 101. Mendelevium Md (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Elements: 102. Nobelium No (folder empty) (Box 67)
  - Eliot, Thomas H. (Box 67)
  - Ellegood, Donald R. (Box 67)
  - Ellis, R. Hobart, Jr. (Box 67)
  - Ellsworth, Robert M. (Box 67)
  - Principles of Radiative Transfer in Far Infrared Atmospheric Bands, Elsasser, W. M. and King, J. I. (Box 67)
  - Emberson, Richard M. (Box 67)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 31 folders (Box 67-68)
  - Emergency Committee of Atomic Scientists (Box 68)
  - Emerson, Thomas I. (Box 68)
  - Enclosed Oscillators Containing Plasma (Box 68)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 16 folders (Box 68)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica. Great Ideas Today 1963, 4 folders (Box 68)
  - Encyclopaedic Dictionary of Physics (Box 68)
  - Engel, Leonard (Box 68)
  - Englesberg, Ellis (Box 68)
  - Enslow, Ridley, M., Jr. (Box 68)
  - Environmental Quality and New York City (Box 68)
  - Eotvos, Roland von. Contributions to the Law of the Proportionality of Inertia and Gravity (Box 68)
  - Epstein, Paul S. (Box 68)
  - Esquire (Box 68)
  - Estimate of Inverse Photo-Electric Effect by Detailed Balancing Method (Box 68)
  - Ethical Society of St. Louis [Mo.] (Box 68)
  - Eurich, Alvin C. (Box 68)
  - European Physical Society (Box 68)
  - Europhysics News (Box 68)
  - Evans, Frank J. (Box 68)
  - Evanston [Ill.] School of World Affairs (Box 68)
  - Everson, George (Box 68)
  - Ewald, P. P. (Box 68)
  - Examination Papers - Ph. D., 4 folders (Box 68)
  - Exhibits in Behalf of Condon, 11 folders (Box 68-69)
  - Expense Accounts (Box 69)
  - Eyring, Henry (Box 69)
  - Eyring, Henry. Festschrift (Box 69)
  - Fabergé, A. C. (Box 69)
  - Fackenthal, Frank Diehl (Box 69)
  - Facts for Farmers (Box 69)
  - Fajans, Kasimir (Box 69)
  - Fallout Suits (Box 69)
  - Quantum Theory of Interface Effects in the Mixing of Light in Phase-Independent Sources., Fand, U. (Box 69)
  - Faris, John J. (Box 69)
  - Farmer, Denney and Leftwich (Box 69)
  - Farmer, Fyke (Box 69)
  - Fawcett, George D. (Box 69)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation. (Box 69)
    See: U.S. Dept. of Justice. Federal Bureau of Investigation
  - Federation of American Scientists, 63 folders (Box 69-70)
  - Federation of American Scientists. Executive Committee, 18 folders (Box 70)
  - Federation of American Scientists. The Fort Monmouth Security Investigations, Aug. 1953 - Apr. 1954, 4 folders (Box 70-71)
  - Federation of American Scientists. Committee on Loyalty and Security, 3 folders (Box 71)
  - Federation of American Scientists. Newsletter, 14 folders (Box 71)
  - Feenberg, Eugene (Box 71)
  - Notes on Approximation Methods in Elementary Quantum Theory, 8 folders; Feenberg, Eugene (Box 71)
  - Feingold, Julian F. (Box 71)
  - Feld, Bernard T. (Box 71)
  - Feldman, Harold (Box 71)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 7 folders (Box 72)
  - Fenn College (Box 72)
  - Fesbach, Herman (Box 72)
  - Fiber Optic Face Plate Invention (Box 72)
  - Financial Investments (Box 72)
  - Fink, Donald G. (Box 72)
  - Finlayson, Lorne Donald (Box 72)
  - Firearms Control (Box 72)
    See: Crime
  - First Intercollegiate Conference on Disarmament and Arms Control (Box 72)
  - First Unitarian Church [Los Angeles, Calif.] (Box 72)
  - First Unitarian Church [Pittsburgh, Pa.] (Box 72)
  - First Unitarian Society of Denver [Colo.] (Box 72)
  - Firth, M. (Box 72)
  - Fischer, Charlotte F. (Box 72)
  - Fischer-Hjalmars, Inga (Box 72)
  - Flaherty, Arthur (Box 72)
  - Flanders, Ralph E. (Box 72)
  - Flemming, Arthur (Box 72)
  - Florian, G. (Box 72)
  - Focussing - J.G.C., 5 folders (Box 72)
  - Focussing - Magnetic, Report from Richardson on ..., 3 folders (Box 72)
  - Folk, Robert (Box 72)
  - Forbes, William T. M. (Box 72)
  - Ford, Kenneth W. (Box 72)
  - Ford Foundation, 3 folders (Box 72)
  - Foreman, Clark (Box 72)
  - Forman, Barbara Friedman (Box 72)
  - Foss, John (Box 72)
  - Foster, Jack (Box 72)
  - Foundation for Integrated Education, Inc. (Box 72)
  - Fourth International Conference on Atomic Physics (Box 72)
  - Fowler, John M. (Box 72)
  - Fowler, W. Beall (Box 72)
  - Fowler, Leva, Hawes and Symington, 11 folders (Box 72)
  - Fox, Denis L. (Box 72)
  - Fox, J. G. (Box 72)
  - Franck, James (Box 72)
  - Franck-Condon Principle, 19 folders (Box 72-73)
  - Franklin, Philip J. (Box 73)
  - Franklin Institute (Box 73)
  - Freedom Forum (Box 73)
  - Freeman, Frank S. (Box 73)
  - A Reply to "Self-Appointed Saviours" of Education, Freeman, Frank S. (Box 73)
  - Freistadt, Ruth Rebekka Struik (Box 73)
  - A Statistical Theory of the Brittle Strength of Real Crystals, Frenkel, J. I. and T. A. Kontorova. (Box 73)
  - Friedlander, Michael (Box 73)
  - Nuclear Photographic Emulsions, Friedlander, Michael W. (Box 73)
  - Friedman, John (Box 73)
  - Friedman, Milton (Box 73)
  - Friedman, William F. (Box 73)
  - Friend (Box 73)
  - Friendly, Alfred. Atoms and Common Sense (Box 73)
  - Society of Friends Committee on Legislation (Box 73)
  - Society of Friends Committee on National Legislation, 13 folders (Box 73)
  - Society of Friends General Conference (Box 74)
  - Friends Journal (Box 74)
  - Society of Friends Meeting of Washington (D.C.), 3 folders (Box 74)
  - Society of Friends World College, 2 folders (Box 74)
  - Society of Friends World Committee, American Section (Box 74)
  - Society of Friends World Institute (Box 74)
  - Frisch, O. R. On the Feasibility of Coal-Driven Power Station (Box 74)
  - Fritchman, Stephen H. (Box 74)
  - Fuchs, Vladimir (Box 74)
  - Fuhs, Allen E. (Box 74)
  - Fulbright, J. William (Box 74)
  - Fulcher, S. (Box 74)
  - Fulton, John F. (Box 74)
  - Fund for Astrophysical Research (Box 74)
  - Fund for Education Concerning World Peace Through World Law (Box 74)
  - Fund for the Republic, Inc. (Box 74)
  - Fundamental Physical Constant (Box 74)
  - Furman, N. H. (Box 74)
  - Future Scientists of America Foundation (Box 74)
  - Gaebler, Max David (Box 74)
  - Gail, Albert (Box 74)
  - Gallagher, Joe E. (Box 74)
  - Helium Iso-Electronic Sequence, 4 folders; Gallagher, Joe Harold. (Box 74)
  - Galt, J. L. (Box 74)
  - Gamow, George (Box 74)
  - Garcia, Jose D., Jr. (Box 74)
  - Gardner, John (Box 74)
  - Garrett, Cliff (Box 74)
  - Excitation Processes in the Solar Corona, Garstang, R. H. (Box 74)
  - Negative Ions, Garstang, R. H. (Box 74)
  - Gasiorowicz, Stephen (Box 74)
  - Gazette and Daily [York, Pa.] (Box 74)
  - Pieces on Pi, Gazis, Denos C. and Robert Herman. (Box 74)
  - Car Following Theory of Steady State Traffic Flow, Gazis, Denos C., Robert Herman and Renfrey B. Potts. (Box 74)
  - Gebbie, H. A. (Box 74)
  - On Spacial Variations in the Intensity of Chromospheric Ha, Gebbie, K. B. (Box 74)
  - Gebhardt, Richard G. (Box 74)
  - Gellhorn, Mrs. George (Box 74)
  - Gellhorn, Walter (Box 74)
  - Report on a Report of the House Committee on Un-American Activities, Gellhorn, Walter. (Box 74)
  - General Electric Company (Box 74)
  - George, Walter F. (Box 74)
  - George Washington University (Box 74)
  - Georgia Institute of Technology (Box 74)
  - Gerdine, Leigh (Box 74)
  - Gerke, Roscoe H. (Box 74)
  - Germann, Frank E. E. (Box 74)
  - Ghosh, J. C. (Box 74)
  - Gilchrist, Mrs. Myla (Box 74)
  - Gill, P. S. (Box 74)
  - Gillispie, Charles C. (Box 74)
  - Gillmor, Daniel S. (Box 74)
  - Ginaven, John H. (Box 74)
  - Gingrich, Newell S. (Box 74)
  - Gladieux, Bernard L. (Box 74)
  - Glass. (Box 75)
  - Glass. (Box 75)
    - Diamagnetic Susceptibility of ... (Box 75)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 3 folders (Box 75)
    - Physics of the Glassy State (Box 75)
    - Radiation Sensitive Glasses (Box 75)
    - Radiation Shielding Windows (Box 75)
    - Solar Radiation on ... (Box 75)
    - Special Glasses for Nuclear Work (Box 75)
    - Strength of ... (Box 75)
    - Sunshine on ... (Box 75)
    - Symposium on Mechanical Resistance to Glass and Means of Improving It. (Box 75)
    - Thermal Expansion of ... (Box 75)
  - Glass Industry (Box 75)
  - Glass, Robert (Box 75)
  - Glassel, Max (Box 75)
  - Goberman, Max (Box 75)
  - Atomic Term Energies in the First Long Period, 3 folders; Godfredson, Eugene. (Box 75)
  - Gold, Louis (Box 75)
  - Goldberg, Leo (Box 75)
  - Goldberg, Philip (Box 75)
  - Goldhaber, M. (Box 75)
  - Goldman, A. (Box 75)
  - Goldman, J. E. (Box 75)
  - Goldmark, Peter C. (Box 75)
  - Goldschmidt, Arthur (Box 75)
  - Goldwasser, Edwin L. (Box 75)
  - Golovin, Nicholas E. (Box 75)
  - Good, William F. (Box 75)
  - Goodman, John M. (Box 75)
  - Gossick, B. R. (Box 75)
  - Gotham Hotel (Box 75)
  - Testimony Before the House Armed Services Committee, Gottlieb, Sanford. (Box 75)
  - Goucher College, 2 folders (Box 75)
  - Goudsmit, Samuel A. (Box 75)
  - Consequences of the Knowledge Explosion, Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Box 75)
  - Grace Church (St. Louis, Mo.) (Box 75)
  - Grant, David (Box 75)
  - Graves, W. Brooke (Box 75)
  - Abstracting and Indexing Services of Physics Interest, Gray, Dwight E. and Robert S. Bray. (Box 75)
  - Gray, George W. (Box 75)
  - Greater St. Louis (Mo.) Citizens' Committee for Nuclear Information (Box 75)
  - Green, John (Box 75)
  - Green, Sidney S. (Box 75)
  - Greene, Charles H. (Box 75)
  - Flaw Distributions and the Variation of Glass Strength With Dimensions of the Sample, Greene, Charles H. (Box 75)
  - Greenwood, Fred L. (Box 75)
  - Griffith, John S. (Box 75)
  - Nuclear Reactions, Griffy, T. A. (Box 75)
  - Grivet, Pierre (Box 75)
  - Grobecker, Alan J. (Box 75)
  - Grobstein, Clifford (Box 75)
  - Groves, Leslie Richard (Box 75)
  - Grundfest, Harry (Box 75)
  - Gudger, E. W. (Box 75)
  - Gueydan, Jeanne (Box 75)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (Box 75)
  - Guilford College (Box 75)
  - Guillemin, Victor, Jr. (Box 75)
  - Gurney, Ronald W. (Box 75)
  - Gurney-Taylor, Natalie, 9 folders (Box 75)
  - Guthrie, Andrew (Box 75)
  - Four Lectures on Mathematics, Hadamard, J. (Box 75)
  - Hadley, Lawrence N. (Box 75)
  - Hahn, Roger (Box 75)
  - Haldeman-Julius Company (Box 75)
  - Hall, Harry S. (Box 76)
  - Hall, Thomas S. (Box 76)
  - Halliday, David (Box 76)
  - Hameed, S. (Box 76)
  - Hameed, S. Perturbation Calculation of Atomic Polarizabilities. (Box 76)
  - Hammer, Preston C. (Box 76)
  - Hamstra, R. H. (Box 76)
  - Hankins, Davend (Box 76)
  - Hansen, William W. (Box 76)
  - Hanson, Herbert C. (Box 76)
  - Hardy, T. Walter, Jr. (Box 76)
  - Harnwell, Gaylord P. (Box 76)
  - Harper and Brothers (Box 76)
  - Harper Encyclopedia of Science, 2 folders (Box 76)
  - Harriman, W. Averell (Box 76)
  - Harrington, Roy (Box 76)
  - Harris, Franklin S., Jr. (Box 76)
  - Harrison, George R. (Box 76)
  - Hartley, Charles. The ?? Mesonic Atom (Box 76)
  - Harts, William W. (Box 76)
  - Harty, John (Box 76)
  - Harvard Business School (Box 76)
  - Harvard College. Board of Trustees, 5 folders (Box 76)
  - Harvard University (Box 76)
  - Harvard University. Board of Overseers (Box 76)
  - Harvey, Mrs. H. D. (Box 76)
  - Haskell, Floyd K. (Box 76)
  - Hattery, Lowell H. (Box 76)
  - Havens, W. W. (Box 76)
  - Haverford College (Box 76)
  - Hawes, Alexander B. (Box 76)
  - Hay, Percy D., Jr. (Box 76)
  - Hayashi, Shuki (Box 76)
  - Hazel, William M. (Box 76)
  - Heald, Henry T. (Box 76)
  - Healy, Paul W. (Box 76)
  - Heat Conduction, Diffusion and Wave Optics, 1929 (Box 76)
    See: Course Materials. Physics 201f
  - Heiland, C. A. (Box 76)
  - Heineman Foundation (Box 76)
  - Hellmuth, William (Box 76)
  - Henderson, J. Donald (Box 76)
  - Hennings, Thomas C. (Box 76)
  - Henry, Ronald J. W. (Box 76)
  - Henry Schuman, Inc. Publishers (Box 76)
  - Henry Sotheran, Ltd. (Box 76)
  - Herman, Robert (Box 76)
  - Traffic Dynamics, Herman, Robert, Elliott W. Montroll, Renfrey B. Potts, and Richard W. Rothery. (Box 76)
  - Herrick, J. F. (Box 76)
  - Herrin, J. C. (Box 76)
  - Herz, Margaret (Box 76)
  - Herzberg, G. (Box 76)
  - Herzfeld, Charles M. (Box 76)
  - Hetfield, Alvin J. (Box 76)
  - Higinbotham, William (Box 76)
  - Hildebrand, Roger H. (Box 76)
  - Hilgard, Ernest R. (Box 76)
  - Hill, A. V. (Box 76)
  - Hill, David L. (Box 76)
    See: Federation of American Scientists
  - Hill, E. L. (Box 76)
  - Hilton, Mary Alice (Box 76)
    See: Society for Social Responsibility in Science
  - Hipple, John A. (Box 76)
  - Hippler, Robert R. (Box 76)
  - Hiram College (Box 76)
  - Hirsch, Carl E. (Box 76)
  - Hirschfelder, Joseph O. (Box 76)
  - Hiskey, C. F. (Box 76)
  - History Committee, Inc. (Box 76)
  - History of Logarithms and the Slide Rule (Box 76)
  - Hobson, J. E. (Box 76)
  - Hodge, Harold C. (Box 76)
  - Hoffman, J. I. (Box 76)
  - Hoffman, Paul G. (Box 76)
  - Hofstadter, Robert (Box 76)
  - Hogan, Mark (Box 76)
  - Hogness, Thorfin R. (Box 76)
  - Holifield, Chet, 2 folders (Box 76)
  - Concerning FBI and AEC Clearance of E. U. Condon, Holifield, Chet. (Box 77)
  - Sabotage of American Science: The Full Meaning of Attacks on Condon, 2 folders; Holifield, Chet. (Box 77)
  - Smearing the Scientists., Holifield, Chet. (Box 77)
  - Holladay, Wendell G. (Box 77)
  - Holme, Gustave. The Electromagnetic Field (Box 77)
  - Holton, Gerald (Box 77)
  - Honzik, Charles E. (Box 77)
  - Honzik, John (Box 77)
  - Honzik, Marjorie (Box 77)
  - Hornbeck, John A. (Box 77)
  - Hosokawa, Bill (Box 77)
  - Hotel Du Pont Plaza (Box 77)
  - Houghton, Amory, Jr., 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Howard University (Box 77)
  - Howe, Harold, II (Box 77)
  - Howe, Quincy (Box 77)
  - Ward Howell Associates, Inc. (Box 77)
  - Hoyt, Rosalie C. (Box 77)
  - Huang, Keh-Ning (Box 77)
  - Hubbard, L. Ron (Box 77)
  - Hudson, George E. (Box 77)
  - Huebner, Walter F. (Box 77)
  - Hufbauer, Karl (Box 77)
  - Hughes, A. L. (Box 77)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H. (Box 77)
  - Shall the United States Resume Nuclear Tests?, Humphrey, Hubert H. (Box 77)
  - Humphreys, Curtis J. (Box 77)
  - Interferometric Determination of Wavelengths..., Humphreys, Curtis J. (Box 77)
  - Hungry Club (Box 77)